<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/categories/laboratory-of-methods-for-big-data-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/categories/laboratory-of-methods-for-big-data-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator, update</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav_2/</guid>
      <description>TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage Digital Twin</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/digital_twin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/digital_twin/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; The project is in progress. &amp;ndash;
TL; DR Digital Twin of the Data Storage System based on Generative Adversarial Networks.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML-IDS</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR A course on machine learning for scientists &amp;ldquo;Machine Intelligence, interdisciplinary perspective&amp;rdquo;. Platform: https://en.pelican.study/.
My role  Lectures and homeworks (python, pytorch-lightning) topics:  Deep Learning foundations: Convolutional Neural Network, BatchNorm, etc. Computer Vision foundations: Image Classification, Transfer Learning, etc. AutoEncoders Normalizing Flows Anomaly detection Time series    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Prediction</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/anomalies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/anomalies/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Application of Neural Networks, Machine Learning algorithms, Reinforcement Learning and Natural Language Processing for Detection / Prediction of Anomalies in Storage Area Network by log data.
Also, development and testing researched methods for improving Digital Twin of Storage Area Network, methods on chaotic systems, OpenAI Gym wrappers.
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Online detection of failures generated by storage simulator&amp;rdquo; (2021) Research Article &amp;ldquo;SANgo: a storage infrastructure simulator with reinforcement learning support&amp;rdquo; (2020) Experiments and intermediate results    Photo by Denny Müller on Unsplash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Positioning</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</guid>
      <description>The project task – build a model that would predict the position of space objects using simulation data.
  https://www.esa.int/Applications/Telecommunications_Integrated_Applications/Orbits
  About Predicting the position of satellites is one of the most important tasks in astronomy. For example, information on the exact position of satellites in orbit is necessary to avoid extremely dangerous satellite collisions. Each collision leads not only to satellites destruction, but also to occurrence of thousands of pieces of space debris pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR We made Space Navigator - a system for automatically determining the probability of collision of space objects and calculating the most effective evasive maneuver using AI.
Stage of the project:
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Space Navigator: a Tool for the Optimization of Collision Avoidance Maneuvers&amp;rdquo; (2020) MVP (2019) First place in the competition of projects of the Academy of Roscosmos (presentation slides, 2018) VR presentation (2018)  Demonstrations and reports:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
