<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bayes stuff</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/bayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/bayes/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What is all about? What shoud you know? Basically how all this stuff works and for what do we need this?
Bayesian formulae Simple school formalue
Bayesian approach сдвигание prior вместо вычисления
Bayesian inference fucking prior, posterior, likelihood who and why did intoduce all this words
Bayesian NN параметры распределений вместо слоев
Applications Sparsification Links lots of them
of for each section?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative models</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/gen_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/gen_models/</guid>
      <description>Autoencoder Variational Autoencoder Generative Adversarial Network Normalizing Flow Diffusion Model </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML-Ops</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/mlops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/mlops/</guid>
      <description>Lecture 1 бизнес метрики обговаривать и объяснять с заказчиком
внимательно проверять данные
воспроизводимость  ноутбук &amp;ndash; это для экспериментов и отчета, методы и функции импортируются документировать все сразу по ходу эксперимента в вики движках &amp;ndash; что зачем, эксперимент, датасет &amp;hellip; codestyle &amp;ndash; линтеры и автоформаттеры (CI/CD, pep8).форматтер лучше чем встроенный в ODE: flake8, bandit, pylint шаблонизаторы позволяют разбить по шаблону проекты: cookiecutter git, версионирование и код-ревью CI/CD тестирование системы трекинга экспериментов: mlflow&amp;hellip; сохранять алгоритмы код в python пакеты, создавать CLI, инструкции по запуску, избегать ручного форматирования данных, fix random seed управлять зависимостями и сохранять конфигурации с точными версиями не работать в одиночку &amp;ndash; выносить результаты на обсуждения  https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RL you need</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/rl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/rl/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What is it? When do we need this models
All this types in one place finally online vs offline etc
Shortly about top models CE PPO Applications Sparsification Links lots of them
of for each section?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraud detection stuff</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_startups/</guid>
      <description>In process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview: a short interview with me on the HSE university website</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</guid>
      <description>An interview with me on the HSE website has been published. I told why and how I came to be in data science, as well as about graduate school.
https://cs.hse.ru/news/741609195.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School: summer school on entrepreneurship (Faculty of Computer Science, HSE University)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</guid>
      <description>Attended the HSE university&amp;rsquo;s summer school, August 22-26, 2022. Wonderful and realistically-sincere event. It was most interesting to get to know the participants and speakers, and the following topics:
 networking search for investment startup economics  Full program.
  Certificate
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics Forecaster</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/logistics/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; the project is in progress &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Deity</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/meta_deity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/meta_deity/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; the project is in progress &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/runners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/runners/</guid>
      <description>Catalyst API Runner Runner – the logic of your deep learning experiment
 data model batch handling logic metrics monitoring systems.  Callback The Callback API repeats main for-loops in our train-loop abstraction:
 on experiment start/end on batch start/end on stage start/end etc.  Metric The Metric API.
Logger Logger for metrics, images, hyper-parameters, etc. Can be connected with comet-ml and tensorboard.
Engine The Engine sets how to run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Computer Vision for teeth</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/cv_teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/cv_teeth/</guid>
      <description>Full-time job as a lead machine learning engineer in the computer vision field at Adalisk.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision Startups</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_startups-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_startups-copy/</guid>
      <description>In process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One script models</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/one_script_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/one_script_models/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; the project is in process &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Images Generator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/img_gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/img_gen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; TODO: description and examples. &amp;ndash;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR A system for calculating optimal collision avoidance maneuvers for satellites based on reinforcement learning.
About We made Space Navigator - a system for automatically determining the probability of collision of space objects and calculating the most effective evasive maneuver using AI.
Stage of the project:
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Space Navigator: a Tool for the Optimization of Collision Avoidance Maneuvers&amp;rdquo; (2020) MVP (2019) First place in the competition of projects of the Academy of Roscosmos (presentation slides, 2018) VR presentation (2018)  Demonstrations and reports:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation models</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/segm_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/segm_models/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Сегментация это
Если надо сделать то берешь последние модели:
 maskrcnn (такие плюсы такие минусы) &amp;hellip; (такие плюсы такие минусы)  Definitions Semantic segmentation – segment category, like car.
Instance segmentation – segment individual instances, like Toyota Camry and Skoda Octavia.
Panoptic Segmentation –
Backbone – the feature extractor network. Then these features are upsampled by a simple decoder module of DeepLab models to generate segmented masks. (DeepLab term)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DL useful stuff</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/useful/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; the post is in process &amp;ndash;
git git fetch git rebase git checkout git merge git pull tmux terminal:
tmux # start tmux session tmux ls # list sessions tmux a -t &amp;lt;session name&amp;gt; # attach to the session called &amp;lt;session name&amp;gt; tmux kill-session -t &amp;lt;session name&amp;gt; # kill the session called &amp;lt;session name&amp;gt; pkill -f tmux # just kill all tmux windows commands:
 CTRL+b c Create a new window CTRL+b n Switch to the previous window CTRL+b p Switch to the next window CTRL+b w Choose window from a list CTRL+b , Rename the current window CTRL+b &amp;amp; Kill the current window  panes commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer vision 3D stuff</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_metrics/</guid>
      <description>Mesh formats .obj
etc
Metrics chamfer distance cross entropy loss in PyTorch torch.nn.functional.cross_entropy(input, target) input:
 predicted unnormalized scores shape: (C), or (N, C), or (N, C, d1, d2, &amp;hellip;, dk) with K&amp;gt;=1 in case of K-dimentioanl loss.  target:
 ground truth class indices or class probabilities shape: (), or (N), or (N, d1, d2, &amp;hellip;, dk) with K&amp;gt;=1 in case of K-dimentioanl loss.  where C – number of classes; N – batch size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer vision links</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_links/</guid>
      <description>My favorite blogs:
 https://lilianweng.github.io/  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/notes/cv_stuff/</guid>
      <description>TODO:
 основные модели и задачи основные статьи мои статьи статью яндекса  Модели крч надо заботать ML-IDS и про модели почитать
доп модели
  diffusion models
  метрики
  слои
  повторить как оптимизация идет &amp;ndash; sgd и тп
  attention
  transformers
  dalle, dalle2, imgen
  пару любимых статей
  как сейчас решается imgnet
  трансформеры
  attention</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Exhibition: Game Junction</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/game_junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/game_junction/</guid>
      <description>Exhibition &amp;ldquo;Game Junction&amp;rdquo; exhibition in the gallery Khodynka with For All Exists Infinity project.
Some details Read more here.
           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker Robot</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/rl_poker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/rl_poker/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Researching and applying the Reinforcement Learning approach to no-limit Texas poker.
  Fragment of one of the experiments.
  My role  Application of existing models Implementation of the pipeline of experiments and comparison of models Development of architectural features of the poker environment experiments Experiments   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage Digital Twin</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/digital_twin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/digital_twin/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Digital Twin of the Data Storage System based on conditional generative models.
  Photo by benjamin lehman on Unsplash
  My role  Generative models research   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Robot</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/rl_market/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/own_projects/rl_market/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Outsourcing R&amp;amp;D project for the Retentioneering company – Reinforcement Learning for automatic budget management for advertising campaigns. We managed to create a quality MVP. NDA.
  Yandex Direct img.
  My team   Me.
    Olga – MEPhI graduate, postgraduate student of the Institute of Theoretical and Experimental Physics (ITEP) in elementary particle physics, machine learning specialist, programmer..
  My role  Searching for a client Management Programming (python)  Environment Reinforcement Learning Simulator &amp;hellip;   Statistical analysis of approaches, selection and analysis of metrics   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For All Exists Infinity</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/art/faei/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/art/faei/</guid>
      <description>Description VR installation created with the Unreal Engine. Two actors coexist, you and AI, representing previous users.
You are able to influence the virtual world, creating traces of presence or artistic images. These traces are a way of communication with artificial intelligence, through joint creativity you can explore the virtual space.
You have no means of communication with your ally other than creation. How to behave in an environment where basic familiar communication methods are not provided?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML-IDS</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR A course on machine learning for scientists &amp;ldquo;Machine Intelligence, interdisciplinary perspective&amp;rdquo;. Platform: https://en.pelican.study/.
My role  Lectures and homeworks (python, pytorch-lightning) topics:  Deep Learning foundations: Convolutional Neural Network, BatchNorm, etc. Computer Vision foundations: Image Classification, Transfer Learning, etc. AutoEncoders Normalizing Flows Anomaly detection Time series     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Atrtigitl</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Online Digital Art School Atrtigitl, 06.11.20 – 29.01.21.
About Artigit&amp;rsquo;l online residency is aimed at a wide spectrum of artists as well as those individuals working within the innovative digital realm. Today the art and digital worlds are inherently intertwined and are rapidly expanding through a variety of formats that encompass a diverse range of technologies and innovations.
The ubiquitous use of personal cameras and the daily generation of video content has led to a gigantic shift within the digital visual landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Prediction</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/anomalies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/anomalies/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Application of Neural Networks, Machine Learning algorithms, Reinforcement Learning and Natural Language Processing for Detection / Prediction of Anomalies in Storage Area Network by log data.
Also, development and testing researched methods for improving Digital Twin of Storage Area Network, methods on chaotic systems, OpenAI Gym wrappers.
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Online detection of failures generated by storage simulator&amp;rdquo; (2021) Research Article &amp;ldquo;SANgo: a storage infrastructure simulator with reinforcement learning support&amp;rdquo; (2020) Experiments and intermediate results    Photo by Denny Müller on Unsplash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Positioning</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Improving the prediction of the position of a space object using machine learning.
About The project task – build a model that would predict the position of space objects using simulation data.
  https://www.esa.int/Applications/Telecommunications_Integrated_Applications/Orbits
  Predicting the position of satellites is one of the most important tasks in astronomy. For example, information on the exact position of satellites in orbit is necessary to avoid extremely dangerous satellite collisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Computer Vision (OTUS)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Runze Shi on Unsplash
  I took a course on Сomputer Vision from OTUS (in Russian) from April 28 to September 25, 2020. The course was practical and covered Neural Networks and Deep Learning in the field of Computer Vision - from the basics to the latest frameworks and state-of-the-art scientific articles. Besides that, there were cool lessons about TensorRT and Server Inference. In addition, the interesting thing about this course was to learn from the experience of colleagues who use Computer Vision in different fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech: SMILES (ML school at Skoltech)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the international summer school SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech from 16 to 21 August 2020. In the poster session, I talked about two &amp;ldquo;AI &amp;amp; Satellite Problems&amp;rdquo; projects that we were engaged at the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis  at the National Research University Higher School of Economics.
Below is the submitted poster and the certificate provide.
 Poster PDF Certificate PDF    Post about Data Analysis for Satellite Tracking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task creation: IDAO (HSE University ML Olympiad)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/idao/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/idao/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Preparing the task for the IDAO 2020 Data Analysis Olympiad based on the Satellite Positioning project.
About This year the online task is coming from astronomy. It is focused on building a model that would predict the position of space objects using simulation data. The task was given by Russian Astronomical Science Center (ASC) and adopted for the Olympiad by the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis (LAMBDA, HSE University).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Generative Models School</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/gen_models_schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/gen_models_schools/</guid>
      <description>Autumn School on Generative Models – HSE University and Yandex autumn school on generative models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference: Space debris</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_2/</guid>
      <description>Participation in the conference &amp;ldquo;Space debris: fundamental and practical aspects of the threat&amp;rdquo; with the Space Navigator project. Moscow, Institute of Astronomy RAS and Space Research Institute RAS, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon: RL Hackathon, A!ONE</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/rl_mts_hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/rl_mts_hackathon/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the Reinforcement Learning hackathon from MTS at the A!ONE conference. It was required to develop an agent for a slightly modified CarRacing-v0 OpenAI GYM environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference: IAA SciTech Forum</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_1/</guid>
      <description>Participation in the international conference IAA SciTech Forum with the Space Navigator project. Moscow, RUDN, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Leonid Gremyachikh.
I am PhD student and Research Assistant at the Faculty of Computer Science 💻 in the HSE University (Moscow, Russia 🇷🇺), as well as a lead Machine Learning engineer in the Computer Vision field at Adalisk. My research interests include Deep Learning, Computer Vision and Reinforcement Learning.
If you have questions or just want to get in touch, then feel free to contact me an email at lgremyachikh@gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>CV CV pdf
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/works/</guid>
      <description>Own projects more details Logistics Forecaster – [in progress] service for the application of ML methods in logistics, 2022.
Marketing Robot – Reinforcement Learning for automatic budget management, 2021.
Projects more details 3D Computer Vision for teeth – full time job, 2021-current time.
Space Navigator – a Tool for the Optimization of Collision Avoidance Maneuvers, 2018-2019, 2022.
NFT Images Generator – generation and styling of images according to the user&amp;rsquo;s description, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First snippet</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/snippets/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/snippets/first/</guid>
      <description>This content is in snippets/first/index.md
pwd </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second snippet</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/snippets/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/snippets/second/</guid>
      <description>This content is in snippets/second/index.md
ls -la </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
