<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PhD: completion of graduate school at the HSE University</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_phd_school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_phd_school/</guid>
      <description>Completion of graduate school at the HSE University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview: a short interview with me on the HSE university website</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</guid>
      <description>An interview with me on the HSE website has been published. I told why and how I came to be in data science, as well as about graduate school.
https://cs.hse.ru/news/741609195.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School: summer school on entrepreneurship (Faculty of Computer Science, HSE University)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</guid>
      <description>Attended the HSE university&amp;rsquo;s summer school, August 22-26, 2022. Wonderful and realistically-sincere event. It was most interesting to get to know the participants and speakers, and the following topics:
networking search for investment startup economics Full program.
Certificate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Exhibition: Game Junction (AI art project)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/game_junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/game_junction/</guid>
      <description>Exhibition &amp;ldquo;Game Junction&amp;rdquo; exhibition in the gallery Khodynka with For All Exists Infinity project.
Some details Read more here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Atrtigitl (Digital Art)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Online Digital Art School Atrtigitl, 06.11.20 – 29.01.21.
About Artigit&amp;rsquo;l online residency is aimed at a wide spectrum of artists as well as those individuals working within the innovative digital realm. Today the art and digital worlds are inherently intertwined and are rapidly expanding through a variety of formats that encompass a diverse range of technologies and innovations.
The ubiquitous use of personal cameras and the daily generation of video content has led to a gigantic shift within the digital visual landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Computer Vision (OTUS)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Runze Shi on Unsplash
I took a course on Сomputer Vision from OTUS (in Russian) from April 28 to September 25, 2020. The course was practical and covered Neural Networks and Deep Learning in the field of Computer Vision - from the basics to the latest frameworks and state-of-the-art scientific articles. Besides that, there were cool lessons about TensorRT and Server Inference. In addition, the interesting thing about this course was to learn from the experience of colleagues who use Computer Vision in different fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech: SMILES (ML school at Skoltech)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the international summer school SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech from 16 to 21 August 2020. In the poster session, I talked about two &amp;ldquo;AI &amp;amp; Satellite Problems&amp;rdquo; projects that we were engaged at the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis at the National Research University Higher School of Economics.
Below is the submitted poster and the certificate provide.
Poster PDF Certificate PDF Post about Data Analysis for Satellite Tracking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task creation: IDAO (HSE University ML Olympiad)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/idao/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/idao/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Preparing the task for the IDAO 2020 Data Analysis Olympiad based on the Satellite Positioning project.
About This year the online task is coming from astronomy. It is focused on building a model that would predict the position of space objects using simulation data. The task was given by Russian Astronomical Science Center (ASC) and adopted for the Olympiad by the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis (LAMBDA, HSE University).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Generative Models School</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/gen_models_schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/gen_models_schools/</guid>
      <description>Autumn School on Generative Models – HSE University and Yandex autumn school on generative models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference: Space debris</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_2/</guid>
      <description>Participation in the conference &amp;ldquo;Space debris: fundamental and practical aspects of the threat&amp;rdquo; with the Space Navigator project. Moscow, Institute of Astronomy RAS and Space Research Institute RAS, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon: RL Hackathon, A!ONE</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/rl_mts_hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/rl_mts_hackathon/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the Reinforcement Learning hackathon from MTS at the A!ONE conference. It was required to develop an agent for a slightly modified CarRacing-v0 OpenAI GYM environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference: IAA SciTech Forum</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/space_conf_1/</guid>
      <description>Participation in the international conference IAA SciTech Forum with the Space Navigator project. Moscow, RUDN, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
