<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>certificates on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/series/certificates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in certificates on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/series/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>School: summer school on entrepreneurship (Faculty of Computer Science, HSE University)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; the school is in progress &amp;ndash;
https://cs.hse.ru/entrepreneurss/#prog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR A system for calculating optimal collision avoidance maneuvers for satellites based on reinforcement learning.
About We made Space Navigator - a system for automatically determining the probability of collision of space objects and calculating the most effective evasive maneuver using AI.
Stage of the project:
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Space Navigator: a Tool for the Optimization of Collision Avoidance Maneuvers&amp;rdquo; (2020) MVP (2019) First place in the competition of projects of the Academy of Roscosmos (presentation slides, 2018) VR presentation (2018)  Demonstrations and reports:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Atrtigitl</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Online Digital Art School Atrtigitl, 06.11.20 – 29.01.21.
About Artigit&amp;rsquo;l online residency is aimed at a wide spectrum of artists as well as those individuals working within the innovative digital realm. Today the art and digital worlds are inherently intertwined and are rapidly expanding through a variety of formats that encompass a diverse range of technologies and innovations.
The ubiquitous use of personal cameras and the daily generation of video content has led to a gigantic shift within the digital visual landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Computer Vision (OTUS)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Runze Shi on Unsplash
  I took a course on Сomputer Vision from OTUS (in Russian) from April 28 to September 25, 2020. The course was practical and covered Neural Networks and Deep Learning in the field of Computer Vision - from the basics to the latest frameworks and state-of-the-art scientific articles. Besides that, there were cool lessons about TensorRT and Server Inference. In addition, the interesting thing about this course was to learn from the experience of colleagues who use Computer Vision in different fields.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
