<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hse university on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/tags/hse-university/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hse university on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/tags/hse-university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interview: a short interview with me on the HSE university website</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/hse_interview/</guid>
      <description>An interview with me on the HSE website has been published. I told why and how I came to be in data science, as well as about graduate school.
https://cs.hse.ru/news/741609195.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School: summer school on entrepreneurship (Faculty of Computer Science, HSE University)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/summer_bus_hse/</guid>
      <description>Attended the HSE university&amp;rsquo;s summer school, August 22-26, 2022. Wonderful and realistically-sincere event. It was most interesting to get to know the participants and speakers, and the following topics:
networking search for investment startup economics Full program.
Certificate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech: SMILES (ML school at Skoltech)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the international summer school SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech from 16 to 21 August 2020. In the poster session, I talked about two &amp;ldquo;AI &amp;amp; Satellite Problems&amp;rdquo; projects that we were engaged at the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis at the National Research University Higher School of Economics.
Below is the submitted poster and the certificate provide.
Poster PDF Certificate PDF Post about Data Analysis for Satellite Tracking</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
