<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>computer vision on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/series/computer-vision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in computer vision on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/series/computer-vision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Computer Vision for teeth</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/cv_teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/cv_teeth/</guid>
      <description>Full-time job as a lead machine learning engineer in the computer vision field at Adalisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Images Generator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/img_gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/img_gen/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; TODO: description and examples. &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML-IDS</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/teaching/ml_ids/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR A course on machine learning for scientists &amp;ldquo;Machine Intelligence, interdisciplinary perspective&amp;rdquo;. Platform: https://en.pelican.study/.
My role Lectures and homeworks (python, pytorch-lightning) topics: Deep Learning foundations: Convolutional Neural Network, BatchNorm, etc. Computer Vision foundations: Image Classification, Transfer Learning, etc. AutoEncoders Normalizing Flows Anomaly detection Time series </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Atrtigitl (Digital Art)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/atrtigitl/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR Online Digital Art School Atrtigitl, 06.11.20 – 29.01.21.
About Artigit&amp;rsquo;l online residency is aimed at a wide spectrum of artists as well as those individuals working within the innovative digital realm. Today the art and digital worlds are inherently intertwined and are rapidly expanding through a variety of formats that encompass a diverse range of technologies and innovations.
The ubiquitous use of personal cameras and the daily generation of video content has led to a gigantic shift within the digital visual landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course: Computer Vision (OTUS)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/cv_course_otus/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Runze Shi on Unsplash
I took a course on Сomputer Vision from OTUS (in Russian) from April 28 to September 25, 2020. The course was practical and covered Neural Networks and Deep Learning in the field of Computer Vision - from the basics to the latest frameworks and state-of-the-art scientific articles. Besides that, there were cool lessons about TensorRT and Server Inference. In addition, the interesting thing about this course was to learn from the experience of colleagues who use Computer Vision in different fields.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
