<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>certificates on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/tags/certificates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in certificates on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/tags/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR We made Space Navigator - a system for automatically determining the probability of collision of space objects and calculating the most effective evasive maneuver using AI.
Stage of the project:
 Research Article (2020) MVP (2019) First place in the competition of projects of the Academy of Roscosmos (presentation slides, 2018) VR presentation (2018)  Demonstrations and reports:
 &amp;ldquo;SMILES&amp;rdquo;, summer school (Moscow, Skoltech, 2020) &amp;ldquo;Space debris: fundamental and practical aspects of the threat&amp;rdquo;, Russian conference with international participation (Moscow, Institute of Astronomy RAS and Space Research Institute RAS, 2019) &amp;ldquo;IAA SciTech Forum&amp;rdquo;, international conference (Moscow, RUDN, 2018)  Mentions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision course – OTUS</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/posts/cv_course_otus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/posts/cv_course_otus/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Runze Shi on Unsplash
  I took a course on Сomputer Vision from OTUS (in Russian) from April 28 to September 25, 2020. The course was practical and covered Neural Networks and Deep Learning in the field of Computer Vision - from the basics to the latest frameworks and state-of-the-art scientific articles. Besides that, there were cool lessons about TensorRT and Server Inference. In addition, the interesting thing about this course was to learn from the experience of colleagues who use Computer Vision in different fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/posts/smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/posts/smiles/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the international summer school SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech from 16 to 21 August 2020. In the poster session, I talked about two &amp;ldquo;AI &amp;amp; Satellite Problems&amp;rdquo; projects that we were engaged at the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis  at the National Research University Higher School of Economics.
Below is the submitted poster and the certificate provide.
 Poster PDF Certificate PDF    Post about Data Analysis for Satellite Tracking</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
