<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>speech on Leonid Gremyachikh</title>
    <link>https://bamasa.github.io/tags/speech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in speech on Leonid Gremyachikh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bamasa.github.io/tags/speech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator, update</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav_2/</guid>
      <description>TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Satellite Positioning</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/satpos/</guid>
      <description>The project task – build a model that would predict the position of space objects using simulation data.
  https://www.esa.int/Applications/Telecommunications_Integrated_Applications/Orbits
  About Predicting the position of satellites is one of the most important tasks in astronomy. For example, information on the exact position of satellites in orbit is necessary to avoid extremely dangerous satellite collisions. Each collision leads not only to satellites destruction, but also to occurrence of thousands of pieces of space debris pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Navigator</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/projects/spacenav/</guid>
      <description>TL; DR We made Space Navigator - a system for automatically determining the probability of collision of space objects and calculating the most effective evasive maneuver using AI.
Stage of the project:
 Research Article &amp;ldquo;Space Navigator: a Tool for the Optimization of Collision Avoidance Maneuvers&amp;rdquo; (2020) MVP (2019) First place in the competition of projects of the Academy of Roscosmos (presentation slides, 2018) VR presentation (2018)  Demonstrations and reports:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech: SMILES (ML school at Skoltech)</title>
      <link>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bamasa.github.io/log/smiles/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the international summer school SMILES – The Summer School of Machine Learning at Skoltech from 16 to 21 August 2020. In the poster session, I talked about two &amp;ldquo;AI &amp;amp; Satellite Problems&amp;rdquo; projects that we were engaged at the Laboratory of Methods for Big Data Analysis  at the National Research University Higher School of Economics.
Below is the submitted poster and the certificate provide.
 Poster PDF Certificate PDF    Post about Data Analysis for Satellite Tracking</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
